orthopaedicshere.com 2014-03-21

# Privacy Policy | welcome to orthopaedicshere.com

We request you to review the policy from time to time because it is in our sole discretion that we may amend and/or append our policy at any time.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit our Site. We may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain or may be tied to personal information. For example, we may collect information, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, phone number, and other contact and demographic information such as age, gender, zipcode, health-related information, interests and preferences. We may collect this and other information when you create a profile, register for our newsletter(s), leave comments or post content, respond to surveys, participate in promotions or contact us by e mail or other means for any reason. We may supplement this information with information collected from other companies.

We may also collect “aggregate” information, which is data we collect about the use of the Site or about a group or category of products, services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and our users’ needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Site. This policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.

When you visit the Site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer’s operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring website, and your activity on the Site. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above.

Cookies and Clear Gifs (Web Beacons).

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies” or “clear gifs.” Cookies are small data files that are stored on a user’s hard drive at the request of a website to enable the site to recognize users who have previously visited them and retain certain information such as customer preferences and history. Clear gifs (also know as web bugs or web beacons) are small, invisible graphic images that may be used on the Site and in e-mails to collect certain information about your use of and activity with our Site and emails. If we combine cookies or clear gifs with or link them to any of the personally identifying information, we would treat this information as personal information.

Third Party Advertisements.

We may also use third parties to serve ads on the Site. These third parties may collect information about your visits to this and other Web sites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our Site (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number). They do this using cookies, clear gifs or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Site and the other sites tracked by these third parties.  This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear gifs in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology.

Third Party Comment System.  
We use a third party online comment system called Disqus. Disqus is not acting as our agent. Disqus is a third party application that allows visitors to post comments on our site and connect those and other comments across multiple sites. When you post a comment on our site, Disqus will collect information about your visit to this and other Web sites, including information you post and your IP address. If you register with and use Disqus, Disqus may collect and use other information from and about you. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, Disqus’ collection or use of your information.  
HOW DO WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

In general, we use personal information we collect to process your requests or transactions, to provide you with information or services you request, to inform you about other information, events, promotions, products or services we think will be of interest to you, to facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Site and the orthopaedicshere services, and for the purpose for which the information was provided. For example, we may use the information we collect:

·                            to send you a welcoming e-mail and to contact you about your use of the Site and the orthopaedicshere services, such as for administrative purposes or to provide you with customer service;

·                            to provide you with all of the services, features, and functionality included within the orthopaedicshereservices, to provide other services or information you request and to complete any transactions in connection therewith;

·                            to respond to your e-mails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints;

·                            to request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Site and our publications, products and services;

·                            to personalize and improve Site content and features and your experience on the Site, such as providing ads, content or features to match your profile and interests;

·                            to contact you about our or a third party’s services, products, activities, special events or offers and for other marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes (including, without limit, to notify promotion winners); and

·                            for the specific purpose for which the information was provided or collected.  

Personal information provided online may be linked together or merged with other personal information so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our partners. In addition, if we receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, we may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you. In either case, this Policy governs this information.

SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Except as described below, we do not share your personally identifying information with third parties for their own use without your consent. If you choose to let us share your personally identifiable information with third parties, we are not responsible for the actions of such third party companies, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these or to any other third parties.

You understand that when you use the orthopaedicshere services, certain information you post on publicly available portions of the Site may be shared with other users and posted on other portions of the Site, including without limitation your comments to articles, name, profile details, images, and messages to other users on the Site. Your use of the orthopaedicshere services constitutes your consent to share this information in such manner and all such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information when posting comments or other information or content to the Site or through the orthopaedicshere service, this information may become publicly available and may be collected and used by others. We recommend that you be cautious in giving out personal information to others in public online forums.

We may also share personal information with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the Site and the orthopaedicshere services and who need access to such information to carry out their work for us.

In addition, we may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or with legal process or authorities, respond to lawful requests, any claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of womenhealth, our users, our employees or the public, including without limitation to protect womenhealth or our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate or unlawful use of our Site or the orthopaedicshere services. Information about our users, including personal information, may also be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership or in any other situation where personal information may be transferred as one of the business assets of orthopaedicshere.

WHAT STEPS DO WE TAKE TO PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION ONLINE?

We have worked to put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to protect personal information while it is under our control. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. You should also note that e-mail is not secure, and you should not send any confidential or sensitive information to us via an unsecured e-mail. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep any password used on the Site confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused.

WHAT CHOICES DO YOU HAVE REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR INFORMATION?

We will send you news, updates and information via e-mail. You may choose to not receive promotional communications at any time by notifying orthopaedicshere either through the opt-out link in the footer of every e-mail or by calling customer service at (800) 637-9382. Please note, however, that you may not “opt-out” of receiving service related communications such as account-related e-mails from orthopaedicshere.

  LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of Web sites to which we link. Links from our Site to third parties or to other Web sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.  
HOW CAN YOU CORRECT AND UPDATE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION OR OBTAIN ADDITIONAL INFORMATION?

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy or the practices relating to this Site or the orthopaedicshere services, or you wish to request changes to your preferences relating to any personal information we have collected, please contact us at  [admin@orthopaedicshere.com](mailto:admin@orthopaedicshere.com) This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it and we will endeavor to respond to your inquiry or to correct, update or remove the personal information you have provided us as you indicate to the extent possible. You may also contact us by mail at the following address:
